brighton.com 2019-04-28

# Privacy & Security

_At Brighton, we respect the privacy of visitors to our website, and our pages and applications on third-party social networking sites such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, and our applications on mobile devices.   The Brighton privacy policy explains our online information practices at our website and other online points of contact with Brighton. We hope the policy below will answer all of your questions regarding how we treat information gathered from visitors. Feel free to email us at brightoninfo@brighton.com with any questions you might have._

### What information do we collect?

When you visit the Brighton website we only collect personally identifiable information (name, email address, phone number, mailing address, etc.) if you provide it to us.  This information may include inquiries through our consumer services contact page, registration on our site, placement of an order, subscription to our emails, response to a survey or fill out a form on the Brighton's website in order to post comments on products or interact with us in any other way, including contest entries.  You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

In addition, we may also use other data for market research, advertising and promotional purposes.

We do not share any of the personal information you provide to us with any third party other than service providers of ours who assist us in providing the information and/or services we are providing to you. To the extent that we do share your personal information with a service provider, we would only do so if that party has agreed to comply with our privacy standards as described in this privacy policy.

Any non-personal information, communications and material you send to this site or to us by email are on a non-confidential basis. Brighton Collectibles, LLC can use or copy all that information including any ideas, inventions, concepts or techniques disclosed therein, for any purposes. Such purposes may include disclosure to third parties and/or developing, manufacturing and/or marketing goods or services.

Any information you send to this site must be truthful, not violate the rights of others, and be legal.

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience  (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website  (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service  (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions
  * Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails
  * The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (including credit cards information) will not be stored on our servers.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### User-generated Content and Public Profile Features

Our website may contain interactive areas where website users might submit comments or other content (including information about the user that might be displayed in the user's public profile within an online community) that may be posted on the website or otherwise published. Users who do this should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., name, email address, etc.) in content submitted for posting or publication, the information can be read and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or parties. We make no representations and undertake no obligations as to the security or use of information you voluntarily include when submitting content. 

### Links to Other Websites

Our website may contain links to websites of our subsidiaries and affiliates, and to websites owned by third-parties.  These other websites have their own privacy policies and are not governed by the Brighton Privacy Policy.  We are not responsible for the content on said sites, nor the privacy practices or the content of websites owned and operated by any such third parties. Other websites may collect and treat information collected differently, so we encourage you to carefully read and review the privacy policy for each website you visit.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at www.brighton.com

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Brighton.com Privacy Policy  
14022 Nelson Avenue  
City of Industry, California 91746  
USA  
brightoninfo@brighton.com  
(800) 235-8748

This policy was last modified on January of 2017
